{
    "subject": "resource/Dorothy_Appleby",
    "predicate": "property/placeOfDeath",
    "object": "resource/Long_Island",
    "human_readable": "Dorothy Appleby died on Long Island.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.89285808801651,
            "question": "Where did Dorothy Appleby die?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8374040722846985,
            "question": "Was Dorothy Appleby a resident of Long Island?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7238917350769043,
            "question": "Was Long Island where Dorothy Appleby lived her entire life?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6934351325035095,
            "question": "What was the cause of Dorothy Appleby's death?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4502960443496704,
            "question": "Are there any records or documents related to Dorothy Appleby's death?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.418992817401886,
            "question": "When did Dorothy Appleby pass away?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4008381962776184,
            "question": "Is there any information available about Dorothy Appleby's life?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.34546175599098206,
            "question": "What is known about Dorothy Appleby's passing?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3221079707145691,
            "question": "Can you tell me more about Dorothy Appleby?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.2211844027042389,
            "question": "Are there any relatives or family members of Dorothy Appleby?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Dorothy Appleby died on Long Island.",
            "html": "dbpedia_4860_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Can you tell me more about Dorothy Appleby?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4860_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is known about Dorothy Appleby's passing?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4860_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Is there any information available about Dorothy Appleby's life?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4860_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4860_23.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4860_24.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4860_31.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4860_36.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4860_38.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4860_44.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4860_48.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4860_52.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4860_54.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4860_66.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'no'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "To answer this question, we need to evaluate whether the information in the documents supports the triple \"Dorothy Appleby died on Long Island\".\n\n{\n  \"output\": \"no\"\n}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\"output\": \"no\"}\n```\n\nExplanation: The documents do not provide any specific information about Dorothy Appleby's place of death as being Long Island. The details provided are about her family, a brief biography, and her film career, but none mention the location where she died."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"no\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 0,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {
        "mistral": {
            "reason": "There is no information in the context indicating that Dorothy Appleby died on Long Island.",
            "category": 2
        },
        "gemma2": {
            "reason": "The provided text mentions Dorothy Appleby's death on June 16th, aged 75 years,  and her funeral being held in Durham, England.",
            "category": 2
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "reason": "Dorothy Appleby's death date and location are mentioned as June 16th, aged 75 years (context information 1) and March 1st, 2017, at the age of 86 (context information 2), but none of these mention Long Island.",
            "category": 2
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "reason": "The given context does not mention anything about Dorothy Appleby dying on Long Island. Instead, it provides details of her death at the age of 75 on June 16th, and another entry states she passed away in August 1990 at the age of 84. There is no information supporting that she died on Long Island.",
            "category": 2
        }
    }
}